{
    "id": "9c99ae8d5cd14bf88f4c409d8e48df08",
    "title": "Relative Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is a writer ................................... works are widely known.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whose",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9d28478492146c0926312d95c2e2b77"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bring me the file ............................................ is on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a7e0c5303e7b42d89753d7bf4beabf92"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ............................................... live in glass houses must not throw stones.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32baf638cbdb4f998eadd17bd9797ecc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Napoleon, ......................................... the French admire, died at St. Helena.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3680c56a3277401195d1bdf8becfd3f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "John, ....................................... is my cousin, works abroad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ae497b9dcf21487581b03ce81748dc96"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy .............................................. fell off the ladder has hurt his leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c79f98f3fb514005922f1abce8055a6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the box ............................................ I left here yesterday?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c54816b10554435b80ff7de3350df60"
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman, ........................................... you were talking to, is my boss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "067ce81f41d74474b3b0d39dd11eaea2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Winston Churchill .......................................... was a great politician and statesman was also a great writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "67ea09d648e94d3e84e0e7d4bbd9f8c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark Twain, .......................................... wrote ‘ The Adventures of Tom Sawyer’, is my favorite writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb16cccc33af461caba5ddfa7b0abb50"
        }
    ]
}